-Boss. This for you. -No, no, no. Come on.
-老板 这是给你的 -不 不用这样
I can't impose on your family.
我不能占你家人的便宜
No.
不行
Yasmin, she made this just for you.
雅斯敏特意为你准备的
Jefe, please.
老板 收下吧
Take it.
拿着
Tell her thank you.
那替我谢谢她
Yeah.
好的
So, listen.
你看
Today's gonna be hard.
今天会很辛苦
We got inspections all day.
整天都要应付检查
Forms to build, forms to break down
要填表格 拆表格
and deliveries all gettin' in our way.
还要应付送货的
We work hard today,
今天咱们加油干活
there'll be a bonus for ya.
会有奖金
And let's all go home
大家下班时
with the same amount of fingers that we came with.
手指头一根都别少
All right.
明白
Hermanos.
兄弟们
Have a good day. Let's get it.
好好干 开工吧
-Morning, Jess. -Buenos dias, Levon.
-早 杰西 -早 莱文
-How you doing? -I'm good.
-还好吗？-挺好的
-Gracias. -Hey, Levon.
-谢谢 -嘿 莱文
No one's been asking you for money today?
今天没人找你借钱吧？
No.
还没
-Why? -Because, apparently,
-怎么？-因为 很显然
I am the only person in the family
全家只有我
who can do the vendor accounting.
一个人会做供应商账目
Oh, excuse me!
让一让！
Hey, I guess we're evil parents, babe, huh?
看来我们是邪恶父母啊 亲爱的 对吗？
'Cause we make her work a couple hours.
就因为她得干几小时活？
Not today.
今天没空和你吵
How about you get those disbursements done, huh?
先把付款单处理完行吗？
We got a line of trucks out there that need paying.
外面一堆卡车等着结账
You could pay me.
可以给我结账啊
Pay you for what?
结什么账？
For 19 years of free rent,
付我过去十九年的房租
and groceries, and high school,
伙食费 中学学费
college, makeup, karate classes?
大学学费 化妆品 空手道课？
-You want me to keep goin'? -Really? No. It's okay.
-还要我继续列吗？-不用了
Levon, can you sign that, please?
莱文 签个字行吗？
-Dad? -What?
-爸？-干嘛？
-Today is a total shitshow. -I know.
-今天乱成一锅粥 -我知道
And you scheduled three things at once.
你还把三件事排同一时间
She's not wrong.
她错得没说
Hi, yeah. This is Garcia and Family Construction.
您好 这里是加西亚家族建筑公司
Yeah, you're speaking with Carla,
我是卡拉 你们让我等了挺久
you've had me on hold for a bit now.
今天能按时送货对吧？
So, we're gettin' those deliveries today, right?
行 我继续等
Yeah, I'll hold.
这是今晚要用的清单
This is what I need for tonight.
太夸张了吧！这是要结婚吗？
That's insane. What is that? Is that for your wedding or something?
不 今晚用
No, it's for tonight.
我们学期结束了 要庆祝
We finished the semester, so we're gonna celebrate.
你才读完一个学期
I mean, you just finished one semester.
-对 这是重要里程碑 -是吗？
-Right. It's a big milestone. -Is it?
-现在流行这个？-听着 这已经算克制了
-Yes. -Is that a thing?
-我在众筹 -嗯 好
Look, it could be worse, okay?
-够租派对巴士 -天啊
-Look, I'm passing the hat. -Mm-hmm. Yeah.
订个包间吃饭
-That gets us a party van. -Oh, my God.
拼命省钱而已
Mija, I can't. I don't...
闺女 我没……
Mija...
闺女……
Okay, fine. I don't need it.
算了 我不要了
Just give her what she wants.
给她想要的吧
No, Mom, I can fight my own battles.
妈 我能自己争取
Oh, no, no, nobody's arguing that.
没人质疑这点
I mean, everybody needs a party bus, right?
谁不需要派对巴士呢？
After they finish one semester. Here.
考完试庆祝一下 给
Thank you.
谢谢
Hey, Kate.
嘿 凯特
Excuse me.
让一让
He needs to get back to work.
他该回去干活了
Get the fuck out of here. It's not your business.
滚蛋 关你屁事
I'm good, boss.
我没事 老板
All good. Five minutes.
真没事 五分钟就好
Hey!
嘿！
I was respectful.
我够客气了
You weren't.
你才没有
Get outta here. Get up.
滚出去 起来
Don't come back.
别再回来
-Vamonos. -Vamonos.
-走吧 -走
You okay?
没事吧？
How did you do that?
你怎么做到的？
We need to get back to work.
回去干活
This one. Over to the right.
这个 搬到右边
-You got it. -Thanks, Kate.
-好的 -谢了 凯特
Levon! Holy fuck!
莱文！我靠！
Was that some military shit?
那是军队学的招式？
You didn't see anything.
你什么都没看到
If Dad knew, he'd shit bricks.
要是我爸知道 他会气炸
Can you teach me?
能教我吗？
Look, my grandpa, he was a paratrooper.
我爷爷是伞兵
Taught me how to break fingers,
教我怎么掰手指
track animals.
追踪野兽
Break fingers?
掰手指？
Yeah.
对
Grandma made you tinga. Shredded chicken.
奶奶给你做了辣炖鸡（墨西哥名菜）
It's good.
很好
And Grandma made you some handmade grandma tortillas.
还有奶奶手做的玉米饼
Why is everyone always feeding me?
为什么总有人投喂我？
If we don't, you'll just eat canned tuna and peanut butter.
如果我们没投喂你 那你就只配吃金枪鱼罐头和花生酱
You didn't see anything, okay?
你什么都没看到 懂吗？
Snitches get stitches.
告密没好下场
Just get my back if I ever need it.
我需要时给我撑腰就行
Sure, Jenny.
当然 珍妮
See ya.
回见
Love you, Daddy.
爱你 爸爸
Love you, too, honey. Get in the truck.
我也爱你 宝贝 上车吧
What's the occasion?
什么情况？
No occasion.
没什么事
Meredith's entertaining some friends.
梅瑞狄斯要招待朋友
Yeah.
对
I didn't realize today was your visitation.
我不知道今天是你探视日
You could let her stay.
你可以让她留下
Yeah, please, Doctor Roth, we don't have to do this.
求你了罗斯医生 没必要这样
You weren't there when her mother needed you
她妈妈需要你时你不在
and you won't be there when Meredith needs you,
梅瑞狄斯需要你时你也不会在
but I will.
但我会
Oh, I know.
我知道
You want to strike me.
你想打我
It's your only answer.
你只会这一招
Violence.
暴力
You're an unsafe parent.
你是个危险的父亲
You're a killer.
你是杀人犯
You can't pretend that you're not.
别假装你不是
Excuse me, Doctor Roth.
打扰了 罗斯医生
Today's my day.
今天是我的日子
Why's your grandfather throwing a party on my day?
你外公为什么在我探视日开派对？
I'm super hungry. I didn't eat.
我饿坏了 还没吃饭
I was waiting for you.
在等你
You were?
真的？
Yeah.
嗯
Okay. Let's go.
好 走吧
-Here you go. -Thank you.
-给你 -谢谢
-Thank you. -Enjoy.
-谢谢 -慢用
I don't need you buying stuff.
不用你买东西
Come on. Open it.
打开看看
It's Mama.
是妈妈
I took that picture
这张照片
with a film camera my dad gave me.
是我爸给我的胶片相机拍的
Grandpa took all of Mama's pictures down.
外公把妈妈的照片都收起来了
Sometimes I forget what she looks like.
有时我都快忘了她的样子
She looks like you.
她长得像你
Dad, can I tell you something?
爸 我能说件事吗？
Anything.
什么都能说
I'm mad at Mama.
我生妈妈的气
For dying and leaving us.
气她丢下我们走了
It's okay.
没关系的
I hurt, too.
我也很难过
Matt will see you now.
马特现在见你
He's throwing parties for her during my visitation time.
他在我的探视时间给她办派对
Staring at me, laughing.
盯着我嘲笑
He's baiting you.
他在激怒你
Hoping you throw a punch.
等你挥拳头
Nah.
不会的
Then he wins.
那样他就赢了
Opposing counsel
对方律师指控你
alleges you have untreated PTSD
因服役导致未治愈的PTSD
and brain trauma from your military service,
和脑损伤 有暴力倾向
making you at-risk for violence.
我为出生国英国效力22年
I served Britain, the country of my birth, for 22 years.
现在反倒成坏人了？
It gets worse.
还有更糟的
They're requesting supervised visits
他们要求探视需监督
and a reduction in visitation from two hours a week
探视时间从每周两小时
to one hour every two.
减到每两周一小时
I have to fight this.
我必须反抗
I have ten grand saved up.
我存了一万块
From sleeping in your truck?
睡卡车里存的？
Court won't be thrilled
法庭不会喜欢你
by your lack of a fixed residence.
居无定所
Hey, I'll figure it out.
我会解决的
Why does Doctor Roth hate you so much?
罗斯医生为什么这么恨你？
He thinks I killed his daughter.
他觉得我害死了他闺女
Did you?
是你吗？
It was suicide.
是自杀
I was overseas on a deployment.
我当时在国外执行任务
She battled depression her whole life.
她一生都在对抗抑郁
You've heard of attrition warfare?
知道消耗战吗？
Yeah. You grind the enemy down slowly.
知道 慢慢拖垮敌人
This guy's got a team
这家伙有团队
of thousand-dollar-an-hour attorneys
时薪千元的律师
who will bleed you dry
会榨干你
until you turn to dust and blow away.
直到你化为尘埃
The best we can do is negotiated surrender.
我们只能谈判投降
You have a daughter?
你有闺女吗？
I got you guys a little somethin'.
给你们带了点东西
Nina.
尼娜
Jocelyn...
乔丝琳……
-Chantel. And Rubi. -Thanks, Mama.
-香特尔 还有露比 -谢谢 妈妈
Dude, these are insane!
老兄 这太棒了！
Where'd you get these?
哪儿搞的？
I have a cousin. Or seven.
我有亲戚 七八个吧
Salud , bitches!
干杯 婊子们！
Thank you.
谢谢
Shots.
干杯
Hey!
嘿！
What? What? What?
干嘛？干嘛？干嘛？
What the fuck are we still doing here?
我们还在这儿干嘛？
He said he wants the One.
他说要"那个"
"I want the One. I want the fucking One."
"我要那个 我要他妈的那个"
What the fuck does that mean?
这他妈什么意思？
He'll know it when he sees her, okay?
他见到就知道 懂？
Do you know how much fuckin' money
你知道这单
we're gonna make on this?
能赚多少吗？
-We better. -Enjoy, yeah?
-最好如此 -享受吧 嗯？
Hey, last establishment.
最后一家店
You guys have early flights.
你们早班飞机
Is that back table open?
后面那张桌空着吗？
It's yours if you tell me your name.
告诉我名字就给你
It's Jenny.
珍妮
Hi, I'm Johnny.
我是强尼
Hi, Johnny.
你好 强尼
Right here.
这边请
My man.
兄弟
You are more than a pitch deck.
你不止会做PPT
Nina?
尼娜？
-Nina, don't throw up. -I'm fine.
-尼娜 别吐 -我没事
She's making her puke face.
她一脸要吐的样子
-Let's get you to a bathroom. -Oh, ew.
-带她去厕所 -真恶心
Cheap! Bad energy.
廉价货！晦气！
Ew!
呃
Oh, my God.
天啊
I hate you so much right now, it's not funny.
我现在恨死你了 一点不好笑
It's kinda funny.
有点好笑吧
Oh, my God, I look mad busted.
天 我丑爆了
I cannot go out there like this.
这样没法出去见人
Okay, well, pick your battles, 'cause we're leavin' in 30.
挑重点补妆吧 30分钟后出发
Fuck!
操！
Go.
快走
Jenny's missing.
珍妮失踪了
What do you mean, "missing"?
什么叫"失踪"？
She went out with her friends on Friday.
她周五和朋友们出去后没回来
Saturday, we were worried,
周六我们报警了
so we called the cops, and then on Sunday...
周日……
She had a piano recital on Sunday night.
她周日晚上有钢琴演奏会
We invited half our family.
请了半个家族的人
My cousin Dinora is a Police Captain in Philly,
我表姐迪诺拉是费城警监
and she says they don't work these cases.
说警方不会认真查这种案子
They take a report and forget about it.
立个案就忘了
Can you help us?
你能帮我们吗？
I can keep the site running smoothly.
我能让工地运转顺畅
No. Help us find Jen.
不 帮我们找珍
My dad was a Green Beret.
我爸是绿色贝雷帽
I can see you guys comin' a mile away.
你们这种人我一眼就能认出
You hunt bad guys.
你们追捕坏人
You jump outta planes.
你们跳伞突袭
And you get those bad guys.
解决那些坏人
I'm a different person now.
我现在不一样了
All right, well,
好吧
maybe this'll help her.
也许这个能帮她
Here, it's 50.
这是五十元
Take it.
拿着
We have another 20 for expenses.
还有二十元当经费
Come on, just take it, man.
拿着吧 兄弟
I'm sorry.
抱歉
It's not who I am anymore.
那已经不是现在的我了
Gunny, it's me!
枪叔 是我啊！
Don't kill me!
别杀我！
I got steaks!
我带了牛排！
If you'd shot a foot to the left, I'd be dead.
你要是往左偏一英尺 我就死了
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
如果我想你死 你早没命了
You know, for me,
你知道吗 对我来说
there's no separation between day and night.
白天和黑夜没有界限
So, I got to make my own.
所以我得自己创造界限
It's hard livin' in a gray world.
活在这个灰暗的世界真难
I couldn't save your eyes.
我没能保住你的眼睛
Sorry.
对不起
That eats at me.
这让我寝食难安
No.
不
You saved my life.
你救了我的命
Joyce would be burying tags in the back yard
要不是你及时出现把我拽走
if you hadn't come along, scooped me up and ran.
乔伊斯现在就得在院子里埋我的狗牌了
What's her name?
她叫什么名字？
Jenny.
珍妮
Jenny. All right.
珍妮 好
She a good kid?
她是个好孩子吗？
She's a great kid.
她是个很棒的孩子
Now, you do this, you better lock in.
听着 你要做这事 就得全力以赴
You better go full on, no half-measures.
绝不能半途而废
But you do, God help 'em.
但只要你做到了 上帝会保佑他们
I told Jenny I had her back.
我跟珍妮说过会保护她
Well, uh...
呃……
I miss ya.
我想你
I worry about ya,
我担心你
but you didn't have to come down here and pretend that
但你没必要专程跑来假装征求我的同意
you needed my permission for something
反正你早就下定决心了
you already made your mind up about.
你早就拿定主意了
Get in here. We're eating.
进来吧 该吃饭了
Hey, Carla.
嘿 卡拉
Thanks for coming.
谢谢你能来
Where is he?
他在哪儿？
Upstairs. First door on your left.
楼上 左边第一个门
"Moonlight Sonata".
《月光奏鸣曲》
-Yeah. -It's beautiful.
-对 -弹得真美
She turned down a music scholarship
她为了去商学院拒绝了音乐奖学金
to go to business school.
说要像她爸爸一样
She wanted to be like her pops.
想当个地产大亨
Be a big land developer.
做大型土地开发
And she will.
她会的
Yeah.
嗯
Nah. No, thanks.
不用了 谢谢
Your family needs hope.
你的家人需要希望
But I can't face 'em like this.
但我没法以这副模样面对他们
When my wife passed,
我妻子去世后
and I left the Royal Marines,
我离开了皇家海军陆战队
a lot of people would've given up on me.
很多人都觉得我废了
But you were patient with me.
但你们对我很有耐心
-You, Carla, Jenny. -Jenny.
-你 卡拉 珍妮 -珍妮
You're my family.
你们就是我的家人
Look at me, brother.
看着我 兄弟
I'm gonna bring her home.
我会带她回家
I promise.
我保证
"Skip's Bar."
"斯基普酒吧"
Thank you very much. Good, bro?
非常感谢 不错吧兄弟？
You good? Yeah?
你没事吧？嗯？
How you doing?
你怎么样？
You need a little aperitif, you know?
你需要来点餐后酒提提神
All right.
好吧
Oh, yo. Wrong house, kid.
嘿 小子 走错门了
Get the fuck out.
滚出去
Hello, Johnny.
你好啊 强尼
Wanna have a race? See who wins?
想赛跑吗？看谁赢？
Hands up. Stand up.
双手举起来 站起来
Place your fingers behind your head.
手指交叉放在脑后
You a cop?
你是条子？
You wish I was a cop.
你巴不得我是条子
Your adventure, kid.
你的冒险结束了 小子
Where's the girl?
那女孩在哪儿？
What girl?
什么女孩？
The missing girl.
失踪的女孩
The one your friends snatched outta the back of the bar.
你朋友从酒吧后门掳走的那个
I told the cops. She ran off. Drunk or somethin'.
我告诉过条子 她自己喝醉跑了
Fuckin' poobutt can't hold her drink.
这傻逼连酒都拿不稳
How's that my problem?
关我屁事？
People lie.
人会说谎
Do you lie, Johnny?
你撒谎吗 强尼？
I don't trust people.
我不相信人
I trust biology.
我只信生物学
We're all wired the same.
我们的生理反应都一样
Get the fuck up.
给老子起来
Fuck you.
去你妈的
Your mind knows you're in the bathtub
你的大脑知道自己在浴缸里
and it's just a wet towel.
只是盖了条湿毛巾
But adrenaline makes your heart race,
但肾上腺素会让心跳加速
so you burn more air.
耗氧量增加
Your nervous system tells you that you're drowning.
神经系统会误以为你在溺水
Your bosses know you deal dope over the bar top?
你老板知道你在吧台贩毒吗？
Steal from the till?
偷收银机的钱？
Fuck you!
操你妈！
You know these guys are next level.
你知道这些人手段多狠
They wipe out entire fucking bloodlines.
他们会灭人满门
Fair enough.
有道理
Just know you're giving me names.
但你要明白 名字我拿定了
Your choice how.
方式你选
Johnny?
强尼？
Where are you, brother?
你在哪儿 兄弟？
You're expecting company?
在等帮手？
Damn fuckin' right, I am.
操 当然在等
Open the door. Fuckin' kill you.
开门！不然宰了你！
Russians.
俄国佬
Fuck.
该死
I'm sorry, Mom.
对不起 妈妈
I'm sorry for...
我为……感到抱歉
shielding myself...
用成就的外衣……
in a blanket of accomplishments.
包裹真实的自己
I wish you could've seen me...
多希望你能看到……
who I really am.
真实的我
Just want to be strong like you.
只想和你一样坚强
What am I doing here?
我为什么在这儿？
on speaker It's better you see for yourself, boss.
最好开着免提 让你亲耳听听 老板
It's not a big problem.
不是什么大事
What the fuck have you two done, huh?
你们两个他妈干了什么？
Why'd they shoot each other?
他们为什么互相开枪？
This is very unprofessional.
这太不专业了
Johnny has no control. He's a weak man.
强尼没分寸 是个懦夫
Maybe he talk crazy, and then it's bang-bang time.
可能他说疯话 然后就突突了
-"Bang-bang time"? -Yeah.
-"突突"？-对啊
Bang-bang time.
突突时间
You notice anything different?
发现有什么不同吗？
Your hair.
你的发型
Idiot.
白痴
Where is my fucking money?
我的钱呢？
You think this was a robbery?
你觉得这是抢劫？
Impossible.
不可能
No one would rob us. No one is that stupid,
没人敢抢我们 除非又蠢又疯
or that crazy.
或者既蠢又疯
This is a shotgun wound.
这是霰弹枪伤口
You see any shotguns?
看到霰弹枪了吗？
-Hmm? -That's nine bands missing.
-嗯？-少了九捆
Ninety thousand dollars of our fucking money!
我们的九万美金不见了！
It's Symon's money.
是赛蒙的钱
Hey, sweetheart.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, Daddy, what are you doing?
爸爸你在干嘛？
Uh, nothin'. Just, uh...
呃 没什么 就在……
Just some work.
处理点工作
-Are you in school? -Yeah.
-你在学校吗？-对
You supposed to be calling me from school?
这时候该用学校电话打给我吗？
No.
不该
Everything okay?
一切都好吗？
Yeah, I just wanted to say, "hi." Love you, Daddy.
嗯 就想说声"嗨" 爱你爸爸
Love you, too.
我也爱你
Bye.
拜
The fucking door opens itself?
这门他妈会自动开？
I don't like this.
我不喜欢这样
I'm alone in the bed all night.
整晚床上就我一人
You eat.
你吃
You come to bed for a bit.
来床上躺会儿
You think the money falls from the sky?
你以为钱是从天上掉下来的？
Hope you don't mind.
希望你不介意
I was hungry.
我饿了
Thought we could have a little chat.
觉得我们可以聊聊
I'm gonna take the tape off.
我要撕胶带了
But if you can't control your volume...
但如果你控制不住音量……
You go in the water.
就下水待着
Do you know who I am?
你知道我是谁吗？
Should I?
我需要知道吗？
You clearly have no idea who you fuck with.
你显然不知道自己惹了谁
Make yourself happy. Tell me.
尽管自嗨 说出来
You have heard of us?
你听说过我们吗？
I have.
当然
Really?
真的？
The Vor.
"盗贼"
The Bratva. The Brothers.
兄弟会 盗贼联盟
The League of Thieves.
现在怎么自称都行
Whatever Russian gangsters
随便你们俄国黑帮
like to call themselves these days.
现在喜欢叫什么
You clearly are somebody.
看来你有点来头
You slaughter Vory soldiers.
你杀了兄弟会的士兵
You steal Vory money.
偷兄弟会的钱
It was a misunderstanding.
这是个误会
I am a brother of high rank.
我是高层成员
You and all connected with you,
你和所有相关的人
will be hunted for three generations.
会被追杀三代
Yep. I assumed so.
对 我猜到了
We all know how these things play out
我们都知道如果不好好处理
if you don't keep them tidy.
事情会闹得多大
Fuck you!
操你妈！
That's for slapping that woman this morning.
这一拳是为你今早打女人
That woman was my wife.
那是我老婆
That's for slapping your wife.
这一拳是为你打老婆
Here's your money.
你的钱在这儿
I'm not a thief.
我不是贼
I don't care about your business.
我对你们的生意没兴趣
I'm lookin' for a young lady.
我在找一个姑娘
I... I don't understand.
我……我不明白
The bar you do your dirty business out of,
你们用来做脏事的酒吧
a 19 year-old girl was kidnapped.
有个19岁女孩被绑架了
I'm lookin' for her.
我在找她
Dimi.
迪米
Maybe you should keep your voice down.
你最好小点声
What do you want?
你想要什么？
Gimme the girl,
交出那女孩
and everybody goes about their business.
大家相安无事
A girl?
一个女孩？
All of this is for a girl?
就为这搞这么大动静？
No one kills three people to sell a woman.
没人会杀三个人就为卖个女人
No one.
没人
I'm not selling her.
我不是要卖她
I'm gonna bring her home.
我要带她回家
Not stopping until I do.
不达目的誓不罢休
Who are you?
你是谁？
What are you?
你是什么人？
Fuck you.
操你妈
Fuck you!
操你妈！
Okay, we're done.
好了 谈完了
Dimi.
迪米
Who are you, Dimi?
你是谁 迪米？
He takes money.
他收钱
He leaves money.
他留钱
He kills without fear.
他杀人如麻
The question is why?
问题是为什么？
Wolo was a respected man of honor,
沃洛曾是受人尊敬的体面人
but his son was never like us.
但他儿子跟我们不是一路人
Dimi is not a businessman.
迪米不是生意人
He prefers mischief over hard work.
他喜欢捣乱胜过正经工作
He spits on his father's heart every fucking day.
每天都在践踏他父亲的心血
Find this man.
找到这个人
And bring him to me.
带他来见我
My name is Jenny Garcia.
我叫珍妮·加西亚
My father is Joe.
父亲是乔
My mother is Carla.
母亲是卡拉
You have the wrong girl. This is a mistake.
你们抓错人了 这是个误会
They're not real.
他们是假的
You're not real.
你也是假的
This...
这……
is fucking real.
他妈的是真的
Eat your fuckin' food,
吃你的饭
then you put on the fucking clothes
然后换上衣服
-and shut the fuck up! -Fuck you!
-再他妈闭嘴！-操你妈！
Have you ever seen someone die before?
见过人死前的样子吗？
Their eyes just cloud right over.
眼睛会瞬间蒙上阴翳
Mmm. You're so fuckin' pretty. Huh?
啧啧 你可真漂亮
Aren't you, Princess?
对吧 小公主？
Eat your fuckin' food!
吃你的饭！
Believe the idea the
听说白袜队要在南卢普区
White Sox are in serious talks
建新球场的消息
to build a new stadium in the South Loops, The 78,
就在罗斯福路旁的芝加哥河畔第78区
the location by the Chicago River just off Roosevelt.
这选址太棒了
I love the idea of being in serious talks
能参与南卢普区新球场项目
for a new stadium in the South Loop.
我简直兴奋坏了
How's it goin', cat? Getting rich contracting?
最近混得咋样？搞承包发大财了吧？
Oh, yeah. Pouring concrete more like.
是啊 天天灌水泥
I'm outta the game. I'm an honest taxpayer now.
早不混这行了 现在是正经纳税人
You talked to Gunny? How's he doing?
见过枪叔吗？他最近如何？
Saw him the other day. He's happy.
前阵子见过 过得挺滋润
Well, you never call me unless you need something,
你没事可不会找我
so, what do you want?
说吧 想要什么？
Lookin' for someone called Dimi.
找个叫迪米的家伙
Probably Dimitri. An associate of Wolodymyr Kolisnyk.
应该是迪米特里 沃洛迪米尔·科林斯尼克的手下
That's a high-ranking dude, cat.
那可是大人物啊兄弟
Mafia captain.
黑手党头目
Legit Bratva shot caller.
正牌兄弟会话事人
Not a guy you wanna fuck with.
这种狠角色可惹不起
Nah, never.
当然不会
This Dimi fella,
这个迪米可能涉及
he might be involved in human trafficking.
人口贩卖的勾当
Can you check NADDIS and NCIC? See if you can get a hit?
能查查NADDIS和NCIC系统吗？
I gotta be careful,
我得小心点
but there's a bar called Hattie's in Joliet,
不过乔利埃特有家哈蒂酒吧
where they sell meth for the Russians.
是俄国佬的冰毒窝点
Maybe you should get a beer there.
或许该去喝一杯
Nice one. Thanks.
谢了兄弟
Hey. Whatcha havin'?
嘿 喝点什么？
I'll just have a beer. You pick.
随便来瓶啤酒
Okay.
行
Oh, hey, stranger. Where you been?
稀客啊 最近去哪混了？
Tryin' to make a buck.
忙着赚钱
You know,
听说
rumor has it you and your shitbag brother
你和你的混蛋老哥
have been talkin' to the Russians.
在跟俄国佬搭线
Rumor has it you were so high,
还有人说你们嗨过头
you accidentally killed Big Mike in a trap house
在毒窝误杀大麦克
and blamed it on a robbery crew.
还栽赃给抢劫团伙
Fuckin' shut up. Fuckin'...
操 给老子闭嘴
Dutch finds out anybody's talkin' to the Russians but him,
要是荷兰佬知道有人背着他接触俄国佬
he's gonna lose his fuckin' mind.
非得发疯不可
Shh!
嘘！
Do you know this guy?
认识这人吗？
No. I've never seen him.
从没见过
I don't like him.
看着不顺眼
Looks like a cop.
像个条子
He's got a gun in his pocket.
他兜里揣着枪
Like a .38. You see it?
像点38口径的 看见没？
Fuck. Yes.
操 看见了
You're up, kid.
该你上了小子
Follow me.
跟我来
Go talk to the man.
去和那人聊聊
You lookin' for somethin'?
找什么呢？
My interests are strictly pharmaceutical, brother.
我只对药品生意感兴趣
Any reason why you packin' heat, brah?
带枪是几个意思？
I'm carrying money.
带着现金呢
Hate to lose it to a man with a knife.
防着拿刀抢劫的
He's a cop.
他是条子
Are you a cop?
你是警察吗？
Nah. Are you?
不是 你是？
Run your pockets, Chief.
把兜掏干净 条子
Let's check for that badge.
查查有没有警徽
You heard the man.
听见没？
Put it on the table.
放桌上
Fuckin' now.
立刻！
I didn't come here to be disrespected.
我来谈生意 不是受侮辱的
All right.
行吧
Let's play.
开始吧
Get him.
拿下他
Get him, brother.
抓住他兄弟
Bye, asshole.
再见混蛋
Enough!
够了！
My grandpa told me to never shake hands sittin'.
我爷爷说坐着握手不礼貌
Look at those bricks.
看看这肌肉
You ain't a cop, you're a working man.
你不是条子 是干苦力的
Been in construction my whole life.
干一辈子建筑了
Were you a soldier?
当过兵？
'Cause you fight like a soldier.
打架像军人
I did my part.
尽过义务
I was Airborne.
空降兵出身
They trained us to jump outta planes
训练跳伞结果
and we ended up ridin' a bus into combat.
最后坐大巴上战场
Sounds about right.
正常操作
Have a seat, brother.
坐吧兄弟
I heard you're in a buyin' mood.
听说你要进货
I'm lookin' for blue glass,
我要蓝玻璃
the good stuff.
上等货
I need weight. Regular.
长期稳定供应
Like four pounds a month.
每月四磅左右
That's all?
就这点？
Who you flippin' it to?
卖给谁？
It goes where it's needed.
自有渠道
The customers are my concern, not yours.
客户是我的事 不劳费心
And why here? Why us?
为什么找我们？
My Chicago connect is missin' in action.
芝加哥线人失联了
I'm runnin' work crews in shifts 24/7.
工地三班倒赶工
Time is money.
时间就是金钱
Seven K for half a pound.
半磅七千刀
That's a Chicago price.
芝加哥行情价
Five.
五千
There's a pancake house
北边高速口
at the highway junction straight north of here.
有家煎饼屋
Be there, 7:00 a.m., having breakfast.
明早七点早餐时间见
And?
然后？
And bring five stacks.
带五沓现金
Good talk.
合作愉快
Now get the fuck outta here.
现在滚吧
Have a seat.
请坐
This is like an awkward Tinder date.
尴尬得像个相亲现场
Just give her the money.
直接给钱吧
Mmm. Lo, and behold.
看啊 果然在这
People talk,
消息传得快
money fucks.
钞票更好使
You got somethin' for me?
带东西了吗？
We don't know who the fuck you are, brother.
我们可不认识你
You'll get a call tellin' you where your shit is.
会有人告诉你货在哪
That's it?
就这样？
Yeah. Uh-huh.
对 没错
Don't play me.
别耍花样
I know where to find you.
我知道你老巢
Yeah. I guess you do.
是 你当然知道
Thank you for not shooting me.
谢不杀之恩
fuckin' asshole.
操你妈的王八蛋
-Yeah? -All right. You ready?
-是吗？-准备好
I'm gonna tell you where the skante's at, big dog.
告诉你货在哪
I'm waitin'.
洗耳恭听
Under your seat.
座位底下
-Thank you. -Keep the burner phone.
-谢了 -留着一次性手机
I'mma hit you tomorrow.
明天联系你
Then you can tell me how y'all motherfuckers
倒要看看你们怎么
built Rome in a day off my shit.
用我的货一夜暴富
Then we can talk about weight.
再谈大宗交易
Guess who's gonna be princess for a night?
猜猜谁要当一晚公主？
You are Dimi's miracle workers. Huh?
你们是迪米的得力干将啊
And that, that is for Dimi's miracle.
这是给迪米准备的惊喜
Why her?
为什么选她？
She reminded me of a painting in one of my father's houses.
她让我想起父亲别墅里的画像
Take her in the back.
带后面去
Sure.
好的
Look how cute these ones are.
看这小可爱们多漂亮
They look like little sharks.
像小鲨鱼似的
Just like you, cutie.
和你一样可爱
She bit me!
她咬我！
She's supposed to be asleep!
她应该睡着了啊！
I'm so sorry, sir.
对不起老板
I want her out!
赶紧弄走！
Yeah?
怎样？
Did they like my shit?
他们满意我的货吗？
Let's just say they were pleased.
相当满意
There's plenty more where that came from,
货源充足
but there's someone you gotta check in with
但要长期合作
if we're gonna do business.
得先见个人
What does that mean?
什么意思？
Precautionary measures, brah.
安全措施兄弟
Seein' as the Feds are handin' out life sentences per pound.
现在联邦按磅判终身监禁
Yeah, this game's not for everyone.
这行当不好混
I hear you, big dog.
明白兄弟
I'mma shoot you an invite for a sit-down.
给你发个会面邀请
Bring your money and wear a suit.
穿正装带现金
I don't have a suit.
我没西装
Shit. You will tomorrow.
明天就有了
'Cause these motherfuckers are as high power as it gets.
来的都是顶级人物
I'm here to see someone called Dutch.
我找荷兰佬
He's right this way.
这边走
He's over there.
他在那边
-How you doin'? -Hey, Dutch.
-最近怎样 -荷兰佬
You bring the money?
带钱了吗？
May I?
可以吗？
First, you gotta turn your phone off.
先把手机给我关机
Now what?
然后呢？
You already have my money.
钱都给你了
I came here in good faith to do business.
我是诚心来做生意的
My name is Dimi.
我叫迪米
Yours?
你呢？
Bill.
比尔
Bill Coates.
比尔·科茨
Do you have driver's license, Bill Coates?
有驾照吗比尔·科茨？
Excuse me?
什么意思？
It's fine. Let him check.
让他查
You drive rental.
租的车啊
We check plates.
查过车牌了
Tax write-off.
抵税用的
That okay?
有问题？
This man is my business partner.
这是我生意伙伴
He is small potatoes.
小角色
I am the big potatoes.
我才是话事人
Tell me.
说吧
Will you be a problem?
会惹麻烦吗？
Is this how you do business?
这就是你们的待客之道？
You invite me here to be threatened?
请我来就为威胁？
Checks out.
查清了
I apologize for that, "William."
刚才失礼了 "威廉"
You are clearly a...
你显然是个
serious person.
正经生意人
If you need resupply, use the burner.
补货用一次性手机
Text bunny rabbit emoji.
发兔子表情
Bunny rabbit emoji.
兔子表情
You made aware I need four pounds a month?
知道我要每月四磅吧？
Then text eggplant emoji.
那就发茄子表情
We are aware.
清楚
If you like what is in the case,
货满意的话
we do more business.
继续合作
Now, you leave and don't look back.
现在走人别回头
Fine by me.
求之不得
Johnny, you're a real piece of shit.
强尼 你个狗杂种
You sneaky motherfucker.
阴险的混蛋
Hi, asshole.
嗨混蛋
He's here.
他来了
-Oh, shit. - -on speakers He's in a black Dodge Ram
-操 -扬声器 黑色道奇公羊
hiding in the trees.
藏在树林里
Okay, we're pulling up now.
马上到
Let's go!
行动！
Fuck! He just fuckin' left on a bike! Go!
操！他骑摩托跑了！追！
Go! Go! Go!
快追！
Fuck!
该死！
Show me your hands.
手举起来
You didn't see us here.
当没看见我们
Nothing fucking happened.
什么都没发生
We'll take it from here.
我们接手了
You're on the payroll too?
你也是他们的人？
How do you know Dimi?
怎么认识迪米的？
What is your business with Dimi?
和迪米什么关系？
Ah, you two assholes.
原来是你们俩混蛋
That man you drowned,
你们淹死的那个人
in his own pool while his wife was at Pilates,
他老婆在健身时
that man was our uncle.
是我们叔叔
He wouldn't shut up.
他太吵了
I warned him.
警告过了
-Do you know who we are, hmm? -Hey. Hey.
-知道我们是谁吗？ -喂
Yeah, people whose ma dresses 'em funny.
老妈给穿花衣服的娘炮
This is fucking couture, man.
这是高级定制
It's our fucking brand!
是我们的品牌！
Tie up his legs.
绑腿
If you want me to be scared, you gotta try harder.
想吓唬我？还差点火候
Whoa!
哇！
That is Vanko.
这是万科
And that is Danya.
这是丹雅
These are my sons.
我的儿子们
My house and my lineage end
我的家族血脉
on these cold, steel tables.
断送在这冰冷钢桌上
Convene the war counsel.
召开战前会议
Excuse me, dear.
借过 亲爱的
Fuck off.
滚开
Oh, wow.
哦豁
Absolutely fuckin' not.
绝对不可能
Oh, fuck.
操
You're lucky you're not already dead.
没死算你走运
Dimi, apologies, okay?
迪米 我道歉行了吧？
I'm sorry. I'm truly fuckin' sorry.
对不起 我他妈真心道歉
She fucking bit half his face off.
她他妈咬掉了他的半张脸
-It wasn't exactly half his face. But... -Oh.
-其实不算半张脸 但……-哦
Thirty-six stitches.
缝了三十六针
That's a lot.
真够多的
To reattach his cheek.
为了重新缝合他的脸颊
I am in the business of pleasure, not surgery.
我是做快活生意的 不是干外科的
Tell me...
告诉我……
Fuck.
操
Do you know what business means?
你知道“生意”是什么意思吗？
Do I... No. I mean, yeah. Fuck.
我……不知道 我是说 知道 操
Business means
生意的意思是
you keep your word.
要信守承诺
You deliver promises. You make customer happy.
兑现承诺 让客户满意
Not bite fucking face off!
而不是他妈的咬掉别人的脸！
-Understood. -No.
-明白了 -不
You just fucked me out of 200 grand.
你害我损失了二十万
If you make one, I make two.
你赔一个 我就赔两个
Customer wants her dead. I want her dead.
客户要她死 我也要她死
You kill her. You know where to take her.
你去杀她 知道该带她去哪儿
Consider it done.
保证完成
Now fuck off!
现在滚蛋！
Fucking off, sir.
这就滚 长官
Holy shit, he was pissed.
卧槽 他气炸了
Fucking beyond. He was this close to smokin' us both.
何止气炸 差点连我俩都崩了
We gotta whack that girl.
得把那妞做了
Fine by me. Let's do the little bitch.
我没意见 干死那小贱人
We are facing a devil.
我们面对的是个恶魔
This devil kills two soldiers.
这恶魔杀了我两名手下
He drowns Wolodymyr,
淹死了沃洛迪米尔
an esteemed captain.
一位尊贵的船长
Now he kills my sons.
现在又杀了我两个儿子
You do understand my concern?
你理解我的担忧吗？
Where is Dimi?
迪米在哪儿？
Won't he know who this devil is?
他难道不知道这恶魔是谁？
Dimi's hiding.
迪米在躲着
They will help you find Dimi.
他们会帮你找到迪米
Thank you for bringing this to my attention.
感谢你告知此事
Now go.
现在走吧
Some champagne?
来点香槟吗？
Your father is dead.
你父亲死了
Tied to a chair
他被绑在椅子上
and drowned in his pool.
淹死在自己的泳池里
So, it's good news.
所以这是好消息
The man who killed him
杀他的那个人
murdered my sons.
也杀了我儿子
Danya and Vanko?
丹雅和万科？
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
You did not know this?
你不知道这事？
How the fuck would I know? Nobody tells me anything.
我他妈怎么会知道？根本没人告诉我！
The Brotherhood treats me like I'm radioactive.
兄弟会把我当瘟神一样防着
Who is this man?
这人是谁？
I ask with kindness.
我是好心问你
I bankroll biker gang with meth connection.
我资助了一个有毒品渠道的飞车党
They introduce me to buyer with real cash.
他们给我介绍了个真金白银的买家
We met for five minutes.
我们只碰面了五分钟
That's it.
仅此而已
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
等等 等等 等一下
I have this.
我有这个
He's hunting you.
他在追杀你
Found him.
找到他了
-Hello? -Hi. Mr. Cade?
-喂？ -您好 凯德先生？
This is the Main Office.
这里是总部
Um, no one's come to pick up Meredith today.
今天没人来接梅瑞狄斯
I'll be right there.
我马上到
-Hey. -Good day?
-嘿 -今天还好吗？
-Yeah. -Let's go.
-挺好 -走吧
Where's Grandpa? He's never late.
爷爷呢？他从不会迟到
He's not answering me.
他没回我消息
I sent him, like, 20 messages.
我给他发了快二十条信息
I'm sure he's fine.
他肯定没事
You didn't kill him, did you?
你没杀他吧？
Dad, I'm kidding.
老爸 我开玩笑的
Do you trust me?
你信我吗？
Yeah.
信啊
So, if I tell you something,
所以如果我告诉你一件事
you know you can believe me, right?
你知道可以相信我 对吧？
Okay, the build-up is just making it worse.
铺垫这么多只会更吓人
I made a big mistake.
我犯了大错
Oh, my God. You did kill Grandpa.
天啊 你真杀了爷爷？
Merry, I'm serious.
梅瑞 我是认真的
Some really bad people are after me,
有些狠角色在追杀我
and I don't want anyone I love to get hurt.
我不想连累我爱的人受伤
Are you sharing your location with Grandpa?
你和爷爷共享位置了吗？
Yeah.
嗯
Can you see his location?
你能看到他位置吗？
Maybe, I don't know.
可能吧 我不确定
Daddy, he's at home.
老爸 他在家
Merry, stay here, okay?
梅瑞 待在这儿别动 好吗？
Merry! Stay there!
梅瑞！待在那里！
Daddy, be careful!
爸爸 小心点！
Who were they?
他们是谁？
Russian mafia?
俄罗斯黑手党？
Yes.
对
They were looking for you.
他们是来找你的
This happened because of you.
这事全因你而起
Violence follows you like a cloud.
暴力如影随形跟着你
He could've left you in there, Grandpa.
他本可以不管你 爷爷
He saved your life.
他救了你的命
I can acknowledge that.
这点我承认
You should go to the hospital.
你该去医院
You'll be safe there.
那里安全
I'll take care of Merry.
我会照顾梅瑞
It's time o let the cops handle this.
该让警察处理了
Cops can't stop them.
警察拦不住他们
All right.
好吧
We'll figure it out later.
之后再说
And, Levon,
还有 莱文
thank you.
谢谢
You remember Gunny?
记得冈尼吗？
Your blind friend who doesn't know he's blind?
你那个瞎了眼却不自知的哥们？
That's the one.
就是他
He has a country house.
他在乡下有栋房子
We'll be safe there till the storm passes.
风暴过去前我们待那儿安全
Hi.
嗨
You wanna come inside? Come on.
想进来吗？来吧
-You hungry? -Always.
-饿吗？ -永远饿
-And you? -Yeah.
-你呢？ -嗯
What happened, man?
老兄 出啥事了？
You fuck with the wrong people, huh?
惹错人了 对吧？
Hey, you could've stopped me.
嘿 你本可以拦住我
What force on earth is gonna stop you?
这世上谁能拦得住你？
It's gettin' ugly.
情况越来越糟了
Can you find this girl? Can you really find this girl?
你真能找到那姑娘？没吹牛吧？
I can find her.
我能找到
I'm gonna bring her home.
我会带她回家
I hear that. You got a plan?
听着像回事 有计划吗？
I'm gonna ask this Dimi fella where she is.
直接去问迪米那家伙她在哪儿
All roads lead to him.
所有线索都指向他
Now, you killed your way into this,
你靠杀人闯进这浑水
you're gonna have to kill your way out of it.
也得靠杀人才能脱身
I figured as much.
我早料到了
I can help you with that.
我能帮你一把
Oh, yeah?
是吗？
Let me show you somethin'.
给你看点东西
After you, sir.
您先请 长官
All right, I will be your weapons sommelier
今晚我来当你的“武器侍酒师”
for this evening.
为您服务
If you come around this wall,
绕过这面墙
you see the Avtomat Kalashnikov,
你会看到AK自动步枪
been killing Americans since 1947.
从1947年就开始杀美国人
Also, comes in a deluxe, blingy version pulled direct
还有从萨达姆宫殿里搞来的土豪镀金版
from Saddam's palace.
这边是M4卡宾枪
What you got over here is the M-Four Carbine,
反恐战争里的雪佛兰黑斑羚
it's the Chevy Impala of the war on terror.
这把MP5 SD适合暗杀
Beautiful MP5 SD here if you wanna kill somebody,
杀人时不会吵醒邻居
but you don't wanna wake 'em up.
但这才是真正的猛兽
But this is the real beast here.
天启四骑士的原始武器之一
One of the original weapons of
M14步枪
the four horsemen of the apocalypse.
你可能记得这家伙
The M14.
不想记得 但确实记得
You might remember this weapon.
拿去吧
I'll have to drill out the serial numbers.
得把序列号钻掉
Oh, no, that's already done.
不用 已经处理好了
These were never here. Never anywhere.
这些枪从未存在过 哪儿都没有
Kinda like us,
就像我们当年一样
back in the day.
来无影去无踪
We did some righteous shit, brother.
兄弟 咱们当年干的可都是正义之事
Yeah, we did.
没错
-What's in there? -None of your business.
-里面是啥？-不关你事
Can I come?
我能一起去吗？
Absolutely not.
绝对不行
What about school?
那学校怎么办？
You'll miss a couple of days, at most.
最多缺几天课
I barely see you.
我几乎见不到你
I don't want you getting in trouble.
我不想你惹上麻烦
Then I'll never see you.
那样就永远见不到你了
That's not gonna happen.
不会的
See this? This is you.
看这个？这是你
Half and half.
一人一半
I want you to hold onto this.
我要你保管好这个
I'm comin' back for that.
我会回来取的
Okay.
好
I love you.
我爱你
Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你 爸爸
Daddy, I don't want you getting hurt.
爸爸 我不想你受伤
I'll be back soon, okay?
我很快就回来 好吗？
Gunny, take good care of her.
冈尼 照顾好她
Yeah, of course.
当然
-Thank you, Joyce. -This way.
-谢谢 乔伊斯 -这边走
-Bye, Levon. -All right, sweetheart.
-再见 莱文 -保重 宝贝
"Our Father,
“我们的天父
who art in heaven,
愿你的名受显扬
hallowed be thy name,
愿你的国来临
thy kingdom come,
愿你的旨意奉行在人间……”
thy will be done."
上帝不在这儿 小甜心
God ain't here, sweetheart.
睡美人醒啦？
Have a nice nap, Princess?
要给你灌点安眠药吗……
We gotta pull over and load this bitch
-靠边停车！-嘿 冷静！
with some fuckin' sleeping pills...
-操你妈的贱人！ -别动手！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-停车！ -快抓住她！
-Fucking bitch! -Hey, take it easy!
-停车！-妈的！
-Pull over! -Come on! Stop!
-抓住那贱人！ -停车！停车！
Fucking get it, fucking bitch.
操！我的枪呢！
Fucking grab that bitch!
操！
God damn it! Where's my fucking gun!
天杀的！
Fuck.
妈的
Fuckin' move, Viper!
快他妈动啊 毒蛇！
Fuck! Fuck!
操！操！
I mean, what the fuck?
这他妈怎么回事？
She is fast.
她跑得真快
We're going back to fuckin' prison!
我们他妈要回监狱了！
Huh?
懂吗？
Huh? You get it?
懂吗？ 你懂吗？
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
懂 我懂
Fuck! Okay, okay.
操！冷静
Fuck! Fuck!
操！操！
Shit.
妈的
Okay, genius,
天才 现在咋办？
now what?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我叫珍妮·加西亚 我被绑架了
My name is Jenny Garcia. I was kidnapped.
没事了 我们知道你是谁
It's all right. We know who you are.
送你回家
Let's get you home.
好
I'm so fucking sorry.
我他妈真抱歉
Miss me?
想我了吗？
Fuck!
操！
Fucking dome the bitch!
爆了这贱人的头！
-You gotta be kidding me. -Is that him?
-开玩笑吧？ -是他吗？
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
Fuck, it's a video call.
操 是视频通话
Here, take the fucking phone! Give me the...
接着手机！给我枪……
-Fuck! -...God damn fucking gun.
-操！-……他妈的枪
Hey, sir.
长官
Dimi says you still have the girl.
迪米说那妞还在你们手上
Uh, yeah, yeah. We still got her.
对 对 还在
Show me she's still alive.
证明她还活着
See? Still alive.
看 还活着
I want a second date tonight, at the farmhouse.
今晚在农场二次交易 一百万
One million dollars.
行 您说了算 长官
Uh, yeah. Whatever you want, sir.
我会把她洗干净喷香等着您
I'll get her cleaned up and smelling real pretty for you.
不 我要她脏兮兮的
No, no, no. I want her dirty.
别让她睡着
Not sleepy,
但要脏着活着
but dirty and alive.
暂时活着
For now.
-操 没问题   -遵命
-Fuck, yeah. -Oh, yes.
-操 爽啊 -哦 没错
Which passport, okay?
该用哪本护照？
You sent me all these passports.
你给了我这么多本
I can't tell. Red? Blue? Green?
我分不清 红的？蓝的？绿的？
-I don't know what color, just tell me. - -Where are we going?
-我哪知道颜色？直接告诉我 -我们要去哪？
What? Okay. Yeah. Go.
什么？行 好 走吧
I take all of them, okay?
我全带上总行了吧？
-What do you want? You want money? -No, I don't...
-你要什么？钱吗？-不 我不...
Here, take your money. You take money.
给 拿钱 全拿去
I don't want your fucking money!
老子不要你的臭钱！
-You take all the money. -I don't want
-钱全归你 -我不稀罕
-your fucking money! -You take all the money, okay?
-你的臭钱！-全拿走 行了吧？
-Let me help you! -No, no, I don't need help.
-让我帮你！-不 不用帮
Fuck.
操
Get away! Stop!
滚开！住手！
Starting tomorrow, rehab.
明天开始 戒断治疗
All you do is let me slip down slippery slope.
你只会放任我在泥潭里越陷越深
You're supposed to be my rock.
你本该是我的支柱
You know, like they say, "Oh, she's my rock."
就像人们说的 "她是我的靠山"
"Hey, thank you." I have nothing to thank you for.
"多谢了 "可你根本不配
You know what? You are just an enabler.
知道吗？你就是个纵容者
he's here!
他来了！
Okay.
行
Okay. You made your point.
行 你表态了
Now we make a deal, and you begin
现在谈条件 你从此
a new life as a wealthy man, huh?
当个有钱人 如何？
I can pay my own bills.
我能自力更生
Congrats.
恭喜啊
-Come closer and she dies. -No!
-再靠近她就死 -别！
I figured that.
我料到了
You should disappear. Take the money.
你该消失 拿钱走人
Make a nice life.
过好日子去
Where is she?
她在哪？
I do not know this woman.
我不认识这女人
You're a bad liar.
你撒谎太烂
Why risk everything?
何必赌上一切？
Why kill everyone for her?
为何为她杀这么多人？
'Cause I told her I had her back.
因为我承诺护她周全
If I give you this woman,
如果我交出这女人
you let me live?
能活命吗？
Because if I just give you the address,
要是我直接给地址
then you shoot me, huh?
你会毙了我吧？
What if you give me a fake address and I shoot you?
若你给假地址 我再毙你呢？
That's bad for both of us.
两败俱伤罢了
Head south on 57.
沿57号公路往南
Then I give you her address.
到了再给你地址
Let's go.
走
You know this guy?
你认识这人？
Of course, I know. He's Viper.
当然 他是蝰蛇
He's Chief of Human Resource Department
人力资源部主管
and recruiting for special projects.
专招特殊项目人手
Why you do all this for a whore?
为一个妓女豁出命？
Say it again.
再说一遍
Please, say that again.
有胆再说
Thought so.
果然怂了
Okay, Dimi,
听着 迪米
tell me where we're going.
说目的地
Where is she?
她在哪？
There.
那里
She's in there?
她在里面？
She's there.
对
Promise?
没骗我？
I promise.
保证
She's there.
就在里面
Why her?
为何是她？
Who decides?
谁定的？
Viper goes to club,
蝰蛇去夜店
takes pictures of pretty girls.
拍下漂亮姑娘
I send them to clients, they make choice.
我发给客户 他们挑
Meeting is arranged.
安排见面
This is my specialty service.
这是我的专长服务
Like shopping for a set of snow tires.
像买雪地胎一样简单
These are human beings.
她们是人！
You think money gives a shit
你以为钱会在乎
where it comes from?
来源干不干净？
If I didn't do this,
我不干这行
somebody else would.
别人也会干
You still haven't told me why.
你还没说为何追杀我们
Why do you hunt us?
为何猎杀我们？
You have a daughter?
你有闺女吗？
No.
没有
Then you won't understand.
那你永远不懂
Hey, good lookin' out.
嘿 干得漂亮
Hey, yo, we good, brother?
兄弟 没事吧？
Man, we far from good.
差得远呢
That motherfucker we hooked up with Dimi
和迪米搭线那混蛋
clapped out half a dozen Russians tonight.
今晚宰了半打俄国佬
Rumor is, he's on his way to Dimi's trap house right now.
据说正往迪米的窝点去
Everybody,
所有人
mount the fuck up!
抄家伙！
You heard the man. Mount up!
照他说的做！抄家伙！
That's funny shit.
真他妈好笑
Sounds lovely, Princess.
听着不错啊 大小姐
I don't condone this behavior,
我不认同这种行为
but my bank account does.
但我的账户喜欢
Hey. It's time.
嘿 到点了
What the fuck are we still doing here? Come on.
还磨蹭什么？赶紧！
Yeah. I'll get the pervert.
我去叫那变态
We're all just numbers, kid. Nothin' personal.
咱们都是棋子 小子 别往心里去
Feels pretty fuckin' personal to me.
我觉得挺私人的
We have to go now, sir.
该走了 先生
Why?
为什么？
It's now or never.
机不可失
Then it's now.
那就走
What have I done to you?
我哪里得罪你了？
Nothing.
没有
That's the best part.
这才有趣
I wonder what you look like on...
我好奇你的内脏...
the inside.
长什么样
The fuck was that?
刚什么动静？
whoa.
哇哦
Levon!
莱文！
Are they fucking shooting?
他们在开枪？
Who's gonna get fucked now, huh?
现在谁要完蛋了 嗯？
He's in there.
他在里面
Shooting the place up.
正在扫射
Everybody,
所有人
lock and load.
上膛
Let's go get this motherfucker.
去宰了那杂种
Yeah, you two on me.
你俩跟我
You heard the man. Come on.
照他说的做！跟上！
Stay tight, stay right.
保持紧凑 右侧掩护
Demon, put it through the glass.
恶魔 破窗进去
You got it.
没问题
Levon!
莱文！
Shut the fuck up!
闭嘴！
Hey. It's gonna be okay.
没事的 会好的
Yeah?
是吗？
You just... Yeah.
你只管...对
I'm beginning to think
我开始觉得
that you do not know what you are doing!
你根本不知道自己在干嘛！
Don't worry, sir.
别慌 先生
Everything's under control.
一切尽在掌控
I promise you.
我保证
I'm gonna cut your heart out.
我要挖出你的心
Good luck.
尽管试试
What the fuck is your real name?
你真名叫什么？
Levon.
莱文
Nice to meet you, Levon.
幸会 莱文
You ready, son?
准备好了吗 小子？
I'm always ready.
时刻准备着
My fight wasn't with you.
本不想与你为敌
I know, brother.
我懂 兄弟
Finish it.
做个了结吧
Sorry, brother.
对不住了 兄弟
-Levon! -What the fuck?
-莱文！-搞什么鬼？
How dare you come in here?
你敢闯进来？
-Fuck! Shit! -Oh, fuck!
-操！该死！-妈的！
Oh, that is not good.
这下糟了
What the fuck?
什么情况？
-Hang on. -Reload!
-撑住 -换弹！
wait, wait, wait.
等等 等等
No, no, no!
不 别！
-I can explain everything! -Fuck!
-我能解释！-操！
No!
不！
Oh, shit.
妈的
Mommy!
妈妈！
Fuck!
操！
Fuckin' bitch!
臭婊子！
Fuck.
操
Fuck you!
去死！
It's over now.
结束了
Fucking die, bitch!
去死吧 贱人！
I think I killed her.
我好像杀了她
Good.
很好
Fuck.
操
Whoa.
哇哦
Stay on my six.
跟紧我
What's that mean?
什么意思？
Follow me.
跟着我
There's an active shooter in there.
里面有枪手
Shit.
该死
Let's kill this guy.
干掉他
What was that?
刚才什么声音？
Bluetooth.
蓝牙
Is that a grenade?
那是手雷？
Mind your ears.
捂好耳朵
Oh.
哦
You ready?
准备好了？
No.
没
Time to go.
该走了
See you on the other side.
黄泉路上见
What was that?
那是什么？
Respect for an old friend.
对老友的敬意
You ready to go home?
准备好回家了吗？
Get me the hell outta here.
快带我离开这鬼地方
Yes, my brother.
是 大哥
He escaped...
他逃了...
with the girl.
带着那女孩
None of this was business.
这不是生意
The devil has what he came for.
恶魔得到了他想要的
Let him go.
放他走
I understand our need to move quietly in the world.
我明白组织需低调行事
But I will not turn the other cheek
但我不会放过
to the man who killed my children.
杀我手足的仇人
Then we will kill you.
那我们就杀了你
The Brotherhood comes before your personal vengeance.
兄弟会高于个人私仇
Do you understand?
明白吗？
I understand.
明白
snitches get stitches.
告密者不得好死
¡Mija! Oh, my God.
闺女！天啊！
-I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. -No. No.
-对不起 真的对不起 -不 别这样
No. No.
不 别道歉
Levon!
莱文！
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢 真的谢谢你
I was thinking about taking Merry
我想带梅丽
out to the chicken coop today.
去鸡舍看看
-Yeah, would you like that? -Yeah.
-想去吗？-想
-Yeah. -I don't know.
-嗯 -不知道
You better watch out for that old grumpy one.
小心那只暴躁的老公鸡
He's mean. He's mean.
它超凶的
Oh, no. He's mean.
哦不 它超凶
Hey, Dad, it's you! You came back.
爸 是你！你回来了
Told you I would.
说过会回来的
You're okay, Daddy?
你没事吧 爸爸？
Yeah. I nicked myself shaving.
嗯 刮胡子蹭破点皮
Hi.
嗨
Welcome back.
欢迎回来
Hey, Joyce.
嘿 乔伊斯
You're in one piece.
全须全尾的
Just about.
勉强吧
Well, I guess they didn't kill you, huh?
看来他们没干掉你？
Nah. They really tried their best.
没 但尽力了
You found that girl?
找到那姑娘了？
I found her.
找到了
So, what did I miss?
我错过了什么？
Well, I made friends with a crow and an owl.
我交了乌鸦和猫头鹰朋友
And there's a goat I taught to say my name.
还有只山羊会叫我的名字
-No. -Yeah.
-不可能 -真的！
It was really cool. I was just talking,
我对着它说话
and then it was like, "Merry!
然后它就叫："梅丽！
"Merry!"
梅丽！"
Welcome back, brother.
欢迎回来 兄弟
You're home.
到家了